

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

## **ILYASSA GUEBRE**



50 Newton St, Manchester, M1 2EA (United Kingdom)

+44 07878839807

✓ guebreilyassa87@gmail.com

Sex Male | Date of birth 21/09/1987 | Nationality Italian

**CAREER SUMMARY** 

Dynamic, Motivated, Analytical and Creative Professional with a vast experience of 10+ years in Information Technology, Competences include: IT Project Lead, Management and Supervision Servicedesk Team, Able to apply ITIL concepts and processes, Technical Support, Master Data Management, Apple Mobile Devices MDM Administrator

#### PREFERRED JOB

ServicesDesk Lead / Sccm Ms Intune Counsultant / Project Leader / Apple Mobile Device Administrator / IT Service Desk Specialist

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Oct 2017-Nov 2019

## IT Service Desk Supervisor & Project Leader

KPMG Italy, Milan (Italy)

- I planned, managed, changed and migrated the all company's assets which comprises: 4800 notebook, 300 Desktop, 5000 Mobile Device (iPhone, iPad) 120 network printers and 1500 portable rinters
- Lead and management of the first and second line Service Desk Team, adopting ITIL best practices wherever possible, providing excellent customer service.
- Report of monthly statistics of the call queues of the first-line Service Desk and second-line backlog, with an excellent result.
- I keep the inventory of IT resources and software licenses updated by collaborating with the IT Finance & Demand department, saving money and avoiding budget spikes.
- Regular user surveys to determine the effectiveness of IT services allow.
- working closely with suppliers, I developed strategies and a team to pilot new hardware, software and mobile devices.
- Attend meetings of the change advisory committee and analyze business requirements by working with key stakeholders within the organization to develop solutions for IT and business needs

**Business or sector INFORMATION TECNOLOGY** 

## Oct 2015-Nov 2019

# Apple Mobile devices Service Owner

KPMG S.P.A

Via Vittor Pisani 31, 20124 Milano (Italy)

- Induction Training and support to first attivation
- ITS OP Infrastructure & Cloud Service
- Mobile Service Owner (iPhone, iPad, Samsung, BlackBerry)
- MDM Managment Administrator (Mobile Iron & Microsoft Intune)
- Enterprise Mobility Management (EMM) BlackBerry
- Supervised Device and Enterprise APP Management
- Wipe and Retire Enterprise Licence
- Mobile Device Repairer
- Technical Support, Troubleshooting, remote supporting &Problem Solving on site



ILYASSA GUEBRE



### Nov 2014-Oct 2015

# IT consultant / IT Governance

KPMG S.P.A

Via Vittor Pisani 31, 20124 Milano (Italy)

- IT Service Management (ITSM)
- IT Process Management
- IT-GV Site Asset & Equipment
- process to Asset & Equipment management
- Guidance and knowledge procedure management

**Business or sector INFORMATION TECNOLOGY** 

### Mar 2010-Nov 2014

# IT Service Desk Support

**KPMG** Italy

Via Vittor Pisani 31, 20121 Milan (Italy)

- Front Office > Front Line and remote support
- Back Office > Onsite support and Ticket Managment
- Maintenance of Computer, Printers and Mobile Devices

**Business or sector INFORMATION TECNOLOGY** 

#### Dec 2007-Mar 2010

### ICT technician

MEDIA STUDIO s.a.s

Via Piave, 21, 23887 Olgiate Molgora (Italy)

- Technical Support and Troubleshooting With remote supporting, desktop, Laptop, printers, mobile devices
- consult and support in local schools and small enterprise

Business or sector Information and communication

### Aug 2005-Dec 2007

### Electromechanical Scholastic internship

Electro-Mechanical Workshop LZ Via Cantelli, 23801 Calolziocorte (Italy)

■ Troubleshooting, Maintenance of Computers & CNC Machine

**Business or sector Manufacturing** 





### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

# Master Executive in Project Management

Milan (Italy)

## Microsoft Intune MDM & SSCM

Microsys Srl, Milano (Italy)

# Apple Certified Mac Technician (ACMT)

Espero S.r.I, Milano (Italy)

# Apple Certified iOS Technician (ACiT)

Espero s.r.l, Milano (Italy)

# ITIL® Foundation Certificate in IT Service Mngmt

Global Best Practice Solutions | AXELOS, Milano (Italy)

# **European Informatics Passport**

Siner Vis s.r.l., Milano (Italy)

# ICL Professional > ICL Hardware Specialist

Istituto Gamma, Milano (Italy)

# **High School Diploma**

ICS Falcone e Borsellino, Lecco (Italy)

Curriculum vitae **ILYASSA GUEBRE** 



### PERSONAL SKILLS

#### Mother tongue(s)

French, Italian

### Foreign language(s)

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING			
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production				
B1	B1	B1	B1	B1			
Certificazione di inglese ESOL International							
C1	C1	C1	C1	C1			
BEPC - Brevet d'Etudes du Premier Cycle							
C2	C2	C2	C2	C2			
High School Diploma							

English

French Sign Language

Italian Sign Language

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user

Common European Framework of Reference for Languages

Communication skills

Confident, articulate, and professional speaking abilities.

gained experience as a public relations between the business and IT department in KPMG Italy

Organisational / managerial skills

Leadership, Organization and supervision a team of 16 people, currently in KPMG Italy Team leader with a proven ability to train, supervise, motivate, and evaluate customer service representatives

Establish a genuine relationship with potential customers and suppliers

Job-related skills

Team spirit, ability and management in work, and perception of individual needs. skill developed thanks to 10 years experience working with the multidisciplinary team in KPMG Italy

## Digital skills

SELF-ASSESSMENT						
Information processing	Communication	Content creation	Safety	Problem- solving		
Proficient user	Proficient user	Independent user	Proficient user	Proficient user		

Digital skills - Self-assessment grid

European Informatics Passport Apple Certified iOS Technician (ACiT) Apple Certified Mac Technician (ACMT) ITIL® Foundation Certificate in IT Service Management ICL Professional > ICL Hardware Specialist Microsoft Intune MDM & SSCM Master Executive in Project Management



### IT Ticketing System

Experience with:

PAT HDA - Help Desk Advanced Assyst - Axios Service Now

## ■ Apple Devices & Services

Experience with:

Infrastructure & Cloud Service

MDM Administrator (Mobile Iron & Microsoft Intune)

Enterprise Mobility Management (EMM) - BlackBerry

Mobile Device Repairer

Macbook repairer

iOs Technican

Mac Os x Technican

#### ■ Windows

Experience with:

Active Directory Services (Users/Groups)

SCCM Remote supporting,

Windows 7 and Windows 10

Troubleshooting, Installing and configuring

MS Office 2007, 2010, 2013 (Word, Excel, Powerpoint)

MS Exchange, Outlook

Office 365

## ■ Computing hardware

Experience with:

Desktop and Laptop hardware repair (HP, Dell, Lenovo, Asus, Acer)

### Printing / scanning devices

Experience with:

Troubleshooting, Installing, configuring and maintaining multifunctional (Canon, HP, samsung and Fujitsu scanner)

## ■ Anti-virus and security tools

Experience with:

Installing, Troubleshooting and virus removal

Windows Defender Security

McAfee Antivirus

Symantec Endpoint Protection SentinelOne Endpoint Security

#### Audit Tool

eAudit Desktop Application

### Driving licence

В